tributes.com 2017-06-14

# Privacy Policy - Tributes.com

**Updated: June 15, 2015**

#### What This Privacy Policy Covers

This privacy policy applies to all of the mobile and online products, services, and Web sites (the “Services”) offered by Tributes, Inc. (“Tributes”). Tributes wants to let you know how we treat personal information that we collect and receive from users of the Services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable including, but not limited to, your name, address, email address, or phone number. 

This Privacy Policy covers the following: 

  * The information we collect and use, including how we generally use that information 
  * What we share and disclose and why and to whom 
  * What "Cookies" and "Web beacons" are and how we use them 
  * How to update and delete your account information 
  * How you will be notified of changes to our Privacy Policy 
  * How and whom to contact if you have questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy 

Tributes' Privacy Policy applies only to Services owned and operated by Tributes, Inc. While other Web sites may be displayed as search results or links from within Tributes, those sites are owned and operated by others, and they may have different privacy policies. When linking from the Services to other Web sites, if you have privacy concerns, we urge you to review the privacy policies of those sites. 

**It's also important to note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you post, yourself, in public areas of the Tributes Web site.** For example, if you choose to let other people see your name and your answers to profile questions, or if you post information or comments on a discussion board, that information will be made public. Your messages and other information you make available in public areas of the Services will be seen by people and organizations not related to or controlled by Tributes, and may be used by others to contact you. 

#### Information Collection and Use

We collect personal information from you whenever you interact with the Services, such as when you: 

  * register with Tributes, 
  * use our Services, 
  * enter promotions or sweepstakes, and 
  * visit web pages on Tributes or on the Web sites of certain of our partners. 

We may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

When you register, we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Tributes does not intentionally collect or maintain personal information for children under the age of 13 and does not offer content targeted at such children. For some financial products and services, we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. Once you register with Tributes and sign in to our Services, you are not anonymous to us. You are free to use Tributes.com without registering or setting up a personal Tributes account; however, some of our services and web pages are available only to those who are registered users. 

We collect information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer. 

We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Tributes cookie information, and the pages you request. 

We use your personal information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. In short, the information you provide us can help us to understand how to make the Services more convenient and useful to you. 

In general, we provide access to your personal information only to Tributes employees and contractors who we believe need that access in order to do their jobs and to provide products or services to you. 

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We do not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you request, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * We may provide information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Tributes pursuant to confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Tributes communicate with you about offers from Tributes and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
  * We may sometimes share aggregate non-personal information with third parties such as the media, advertisers, and government agencies. This aggregate information is typically in the form of statistics, such as numbers of Tributes users who live in a particular state or fall within a particular age group. Such aggregate information is gathered from individual Tributes users' information but is not traceable to any specific identifiable Tributes user. 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Tributes terms of use, or as otherwise required or permitted by law. 

#### Our Advertisers

We do not share your personal information with our advertisers. However, the advertising we display is targeted to users of particular services and content. So if you view or click on a targeted ad, the advertiser (or other companies affiliated with the advertiser) may assume that you meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 50-60 from a particular geographic area or with children or grandchildren of a certain age. 

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

Tributes, like many Web sites, uses cookies to prepare customized Web pages for you within the Services. A cookie is a file containing a string of code that we transfer to your computer's hard drive, to be kept there for later use. With cookies in place, whenever you use your Web browser to connect to the Services, our systems are able to recognize you. This enables Tributes to present you with custom Web pages. So, for example, instead of seeing just a generic welcome page, you see a welcome page with your name on it and information that relates to where you live (your zip code) and products or services that reflect your interests. 

In addition to Tributes' cookies, when you visit Tributes your computer may receive cookies from our advertisers, and from other sites displayed as search results or links. The cookies inserted by those third parties are not covered by Tributes' Privacy Policy, but rather, by the policies of those advertisers and outside Web sites. 

You can set up your browser to reject cookies or tell you when a cookie has been sent. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of the Services’ interactive features, and we hope you will leave them turned on. Tributes also uses web beacons (also known as action tags or single pixel gifs) to access Tributes cookies inside and outside our Web pages and in connection with Tributes products and services. A web beacon is a transparent image placed on a web page that sends a signal when a person visits that page. This enables us to assess the popularity and effectiveness of the material posted on the Tributes Web site. We may also use web beacons in connection with e-mails sent to Tributes users, to let us know whether and when the e-mail was opened. No personal information is transmitted through web beacons. 

#### Third-party Ad Serving

Tributes contracts with third party companies to help us make sure that our content and advertising are relevant and effective, and to analyze how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing company on this site. The type of information we collect includes, for example, the pages you visited at Tributes. This information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which products are most interesting, and what kinds of offers our visitors like to see. Although our third party marketing partners manage the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. 

The ads on Tributes pages are delivered to you by ad serving services including DoubleClick, our web advertising partner. Information about your visit to Tributes, such as number of times you have viewed an ad, is used to serve ads to you whenever you visit Tributes. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to opt out, please [click here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx). 

#### Online Tracking

Some browsers allow you to indicate that you would not like your online activities tracked, using "Do Not Track" indicators ("DNT Indicators"), however, we are not obligated to respond to these indicators. Presently, we are not set up to respond to DNT Indicators. This means that while the Services may track certain information about your online activities, the collected information will be used to improve your use of our Services and in ways consistent with the provisions of this Privacy Policy. 

#### Your Ability to Update and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

You can update your Tributes Account Information, including your biographical and profile information, at any time, by going to the My Account page. 

New categories of marketing communications may be added to the My Account page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 

We reserve the right to send you certain important communications relating to the Services, such as service announcements and administrative messages, throughout the term of your personal Tributes account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving these important communications. 

You can terminate your Tributes account at any time by sending a request to [tributes@legacy.com](mailto:tributes@legacy.com). 

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Tributes account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

#### Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, please complete a feedback form or you can contact us at: 

Tributes, Inc.   
c/o Legacy.com, Inc.   
820 Davis Street, Suite 210   
Evanston, IL 60201   

#### YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

(As provided by California Civil Code Section 1798.83) 

A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes ("California customer") is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. 

Tributes does not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. 

California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by emailing tributes@legacy.com. 

**Effective Date: June 15, 2015**
